const harryPotter1q1 = {
    question: 'In what year was the first Harry Potter movie released?',
    selection: ['A. 1999', 'B. 2001', 'C. 2002', 'D. 2000'],
    answer: 'B.2001'
}
const harryPotter1q2 = {
    question: 'What does the acronym O.W.L. stand for?',
    selection: ['A. Original Wizarding Latitudes', 'B. Ordinary Witching Lights', 'C. Ordinary Wizarding Levels', 'D. Original Witching Loans'],
    answer: 'C. Ordinary Wizarding Levels'
}
const harryPotter1q3 = {
    question: 'What kind of creature does the groundskeeper, Hagrid, love most of all?',
    selection: ['A. Thestral', 'B. Mandrake', 'C. Hippogriff', 'D. Dragon'],
    answer: 'D. Dragon'
}
const harryPotter1q4 = {
    question: 'How many staircases does Hogwarts have?',
    selection: ['A. 245', 'B. 74', 'C. 142', 'D. 1482'],
    answer: 'C. 142'
}
const harryPotter1q5 = {
    question: 'What is the real name of the Dark Lord Voldemort?',
    selection: ['A. Tom Marvolo Riddle', 'B. Lucious Malfoy', 'C. Gelert Grindelvald', 'D. Aberforth Dumbledore'],
    answer: 'A. Tom Marvolo Riddle'
}
const harryPotter1q6 = {
    question: 'In the Harry Potter universe; Who wrote the book "Hogwarts, A History"?',
    selection: ['A. Bathilda Bagshot', 'B. Gildory Lockheart', 'C. Severus Snape', 'D. Newt Skemander'],
    answer: 'A. Bathilda Bagshot'
}
const harryPotter1q7 = {
    question: 'When using the killing curse, what words would you speak?',
    selection: ['A. Bombarda', 'B. Sectumsempra', 'C. Expecto Patronus', 'D. Avada Kedavra'],
    answer: 'D. Avada Kedavra'
}
const harryPotter1q8 = {
    question: 'What is the name of the bank in Diagon Alley?',
    selection: ['A. Olivanders', 'B. Gringotts', 'C. Borgin & Burkes', 'D. The Three Broomsticks'],
    answer: 'C. Borgin & Burkes'
}
const harryPotter1q9 = {
    question: 'Who is Sirius Black?',
    selection: ['A. Harry`s Dad', 'B. Harry`s Uncle', 'C. Harry`s Brother', 'D. Harry`s Godfather'],
    answer: 'D. Harry`s Godfather'
}
const harryPotter1q10 = {
    question: 'What is the name of someone born into the wizarding world who CANNOT do magic?',
    selection: ['A. Muggle', 'B. Squib', 'C. Mudblood', 'D. Noob'],
    answer: 'C. Mudblood'
}